{
    "subject": "resource/Morte",
    "predicate": "property/voice",
    "object": "resource/Rob_Paulsen",
    "human_readable": "Morte is voiced by Rob Paulsen.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8991312980651855,
            "question": "How does Rob Paulsen's voice contribute to the character Morte?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7731615304946899,
            "question": "Who voices the character Morte?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7274882793426514,
            "question": "Is Rob Paulsen a famous voice actor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6685410737991333,
            "question": "Can you name other characters voiced by Rob Paulsen?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3939336836338043,
            "question": "What is Rob Paulsen known for voicing?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.24672022461891174,
            "question": "In what type of media does Morte appear?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.24030490219593048,
            "question": "What are some characteristics of the character Morte?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1629772186279297,
            "question": "Who are some other notable voice actors?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.07207565009593964,
            "question": "What is the significance of voice acting in entertainment?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.06817927956581116,
            "question": "What makes a good voice actor?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Morte is voiced by Rob Paulsen.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2500_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the significance of voice acting in entertainment?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2500_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who are some other notable voice actors?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2500_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some characteristics of the character Morte?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2500_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2500_103.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2500_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2500_123.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2500_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2500_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2500_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2500_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2500_82.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2500_92.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2500_97.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe information provided in the documents supports that Morte, from the game context, is indeed voiced by Rob Paulsen."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}